tekkaus.com 2012-12-11

# Tekkaus.com Privacy Policy | Tekkaus

[Tekkaus.com](http://www.tekkaus.com/) is a personal, general, lifestyle blog maintained by the [**author-Tekkaus**](http://www.tekkaus.com/2010/03/about-me-author.html) (not my real name). I want to let all my readers and website visitors know that I am committed to protecting your provacy and providing a safe online experience to all my visitors while you are here. When you are visiting this site of mine-Tekkaus.com, **I recognize that privacy of your personal information is very important**. And that's precisely why I have decided to include the following, which discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this blog. Rest assured that none of your private information such as email will be shared nor sold to anyone.

 **Blog Disclaimer**

First and foremost, you have to understand that this is a content rich blog whereby everything shared in this blog is for informational and entertainment purposes. I will not be responsible for any of the information shared on this blog. I am not providing any medical, legal or professional advice. It should be clear that you are reading this blog on your own free will and you are taking the information provided at your own risk. If you need any advice or solution, you are encouraged to seek for professional consultation.

 **Log Files**

Like all the other websites and blogs, this blog also collect and use data collected in log files.The information in your log files include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, the country you are at that particular moment, the type of web browser you are using to surf this blog, your ISP (Internet Service Provider) such as Streamyx if you are from Malaysia, your referring and exit pages, the OS (Operating System) of the computer you are using, the date and time, and the number of clicks being performed in this blog. All these information will be used to analyze trends, track visitors activity and interest, to gather demographic information and more importantly to administer this blog.

 **Web Cookies and Advertising Companies**

This blog uses cookies to store information. Web cookies are parcels of text that are sent by a web server to a web browser (Firefox, Chrome, IE etc.) and in turn, they are sent back in their intact form by the browser each time it accesses the server. In other words, cookies store visitors' preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access of visit.

Moreover I also use third party advertisement on Tekkaus.com to support this blog. Please bear in mind that some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies when their advertisements are shown in this blog. Hence your information including your IP address, your ISP, the type of browser your use etc. will be sent to these advertisers (such as Google through Google Adsense program). Do not worry as this is generally used for geotagging purposes or to show ads on specific posts visited.

I am currently working with several advertising companies and networks, such as: ([Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy.html), [Nuffnang](http://www.nuffnang.com.my/privacy-policy/), [Infolinks](http://www.infolinks.com/privacy.html), [Chitika](http://chitika.com/privacy_policy.php) just to name a few). If you have any doubts and questions please click to find out more about the respective privacy policy of these companies.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual web browser options. Please check your respective web browsers help section for instruction on how to disable cookies during your visits at this blog.

 **Links**

This blog may contains links to other blogs, websites, forums etc. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. I strongly encourage you to read the respective privacy policy of the other sites when you leave this blog of mine. This privacy policy applies solely to my blog.

If you need any clarification regarding Tekkaus.com privacy policy please feel free to contact me immediately. I can be reached at [tekkaus@gmail.com](mailto:tekkaus@gmail.com). Thanks for visiting this blog.

**About Tekkaus**  
Tekkaus is the founder and editor of [Tekkaus](http://www.tekkaus.com/) and [World Lense](http://worldlense.blogspot.com/). I am a lifestyle blogger who write just about anything, emphasizing on blogging tips, social media, gadgets, music, my family and more. Learn more about me [here](http://www.tekkaus.com/2010/03/about-me-author.html). Subscribe to my [feed](http://feeds.feedburner.com/tekkaus/feed) and my facebook [page](http://www.facebook.com/Tekkausdotcom). Do connect with me on [Twitter](http://twitter.com/tekkaus)
